THE INVISIBLE FROG  |  GLASS FROG
IN THE TROPICAL RAINFORESTS,
THE DENSE GREENERY IS A SAFE HAVEN.
LIFE CAN HIDE IN PLAIN SIGHT.
FOR THIS GLASS FROG,
CAMOUFLAGE IS EFFORTLESS.
IT HAS MASTERED THE
ART OF INVISIBILITY.
THEY AREN'T NAMED FOR
THEIR FRAGILITY...
THEIR BONES, INTESTINES & BEATING HEARTS
CAN BE SEEN THROUGH THEIR SKIN.
THEY'RE TRANSLUCENT WITH THE SKIN
ON THEIR BACKS VIVID GREEN.
THIS ALLOWS THEM TO BRIGHTEN OR DARKEN
DEPENDING ON THE BACKGROUND.
THEIR SEE-THROUGH LEGS BREAK UP OUTLINES
BLENDING THEM SMOOTHLY INTO LEAVES.
THIS UNIQUE PHENOMENON IS KNOWN AS
EDGE DIFFUSION.
IN THE GAME OF HIDE AND SEEK,
THEY OUTWIT EVERY PREDATOR.
A MASTERCLASS IN STEALTH AND SURVIVAL
IN THE DENSE RAINFOREST.